A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller personal papers, Art, Series C FA340
Rockefeller Archive Center
- CKU Reference Files, 1949-1979; 3; 27.6 Cubic Feet
  - NAR Collection Numbering Lists, 1948, 1963-1968 (Box 45, Folder 374)
  - The New School Art Center - Correspondence, 1964-1967 (Box 46, Folder 375)
    Correspondence re exhibition catalog. Draft of catalog text. Lists of artworks to be displayed.
  - The New School Art Center - Catalog (Box 46, Folder 376)
    Memoranda, and news clippings from a previous exhibit.
  - The New School Art Center - Speech, 1967-1971 (Box 46, Folder 377)
    Text of speech given by NAR. Lists of slides which accompanied speech. Background material for the speech.
  - The New School Art Center - Speech, 1967-1971 (Box 46, Folder 378)
  - NRC Memos to Dick Parsons, 1978 (Box 46, Folder 379)
    Memoranda re reproduction rights and authenticity of NAR artworks used as part of the NRC (Nelson Rockefeller Collection). Catalog cards and sheets.
  - NRC Memos to Dick Parsons, 1978 (Box 46, Folder 380)
  - NRC Memos to Dick Parsons, 1978 (Box 46, Folder 0380A)
  - NRC Memos to Dick Parsons, 1978 (Box 46, Folder 381)
  - NRC Memos to Dick Parsons, 1978 (Box 46, Folder 382)
  - Oak Ridge Community Art Center - Oi (Box 47, Folder 383)
    Oak Ridge Community Art Center, Inc. O'Brien, Donald C. Jr. O'Brien, Edward F. O'Brien, Robert E. O'Connor, Bernice Odio, Eunice Odle, Daniel O'Donnell, Mary Ellen O'Donnell, Sally Miller O'Drsicoll, L.P. Of Westchester O'Gatty, James Ogden, Peter O'Grady, Jack W. (Jack O'Grady Galleries) O'Hara, General A.C. Oi, Motoi
  - Okada - Okubo (Box 47, Folder 384)
    Okada, Kenzo Oklahoma Okubo, Min
  - Olbrecht - Omer (Box 47, Folder 385)
    Olbrecht, Frans M. Old Print Shop, The Olean Public Library O'Leary, Maria Teresa Olivetti Underwood Corporation H.G. Ollendorff, Inc. Olsen, Betty Olson, Patricia Olson, Roberta Omer, Mordechai
  - O'Neill - Ortuzar (Box 47, Folder 386)
    O'Neill, Anne O'Neill, Catherine C. O'Neill, Harry O'Neill, Lois Decker Operation Buddy, Inc. Oppenheim, S. Edmund Oravsky, Mrs. Frank Ordover, Jerald Orenstein, Jack Oriental Oriental Art Oriental Ceramics Oriental Scroll Box Origins of Art Research Foundation Orozco, Margarita V.(re Jose Clemente Orozco) Orozco, Jose Clemente Orr, Frederick W. 2nd Ortiz, W. Ortiz, Ralph Ortona, Edigio Ortuzar, Mariano
  - Osborn - Oyen (Box 47, Folder 387)
    Osborn, Charles L. Osborne, Alice S. Lily de Jorigh Osborne Osborne, Vlada Benko Oscar, Lisa Osterweil, Michael O'Toole, James St. L. Ould, Mrs. James P. Jr Our Lady of Lourdes Hospital Outcalt, A. Ruth Overley, Margaret Overseas Purchases Owen, Walter F. II Oyen, Edwin J.
  - O'Neill, Abby and George, Jr. (CLOSED FOLDER), 1974-1975 (Box 47, Folder 388)
  - Pace College - Pajic (Box 47, Folder 389)
    Pace College Pace Gallery Pacheco, Maria Luisa Pack, Mrs. Benteley Ruben Pacheco Polo Pack, Frank Packing cases Padgett, Charles Paez, George Paintings from Private Collections, 1955 Pajic, Predrag
  - Palais de la Mediterranee - Paperweights (Box 47, Folder 390)
    Palais de la Mditerrane, Nice Palazzo, Salvador Paley, Stewart Pallotti, Noemi Palmieri, Giuseppe Pan American Union Pan, Mrs. Chung Yee Pan, Mr. Li Sun Pangallo, Jane Panzer, Samuel Paolozzi, Eduardo Paperweights
  - Paragon Books - Pastizzo (Box 47, Folder 391)
    Paragon Books Pari, Mrs. Jack M. Parke-Bernat Galleries Parker, Theresa Parkside Displays Parma Gallery Parrish Art Museum Parsell, Palmyre S. Parsons, Betty (Betty Parsons Gallery) Parsons, Patricia Parsons, Robert Partington, Susan Partridge, Frank Jr. Parylak, Robert Pasadena Art Museum Pascal Pastizzo, Michael R.
  - Patafio - Paylo (Box 48, Folder 392)
    Paterson, Anthony R. Patricelli, Susan Patterson, H.R. Patterson, Marion B. Patzold, F.J. Paules, Dean L. Pauley, Hal Paxton, John L. Paylo, Kenneth J.
  - Peabody - Penn (William) Memorial Museum (Box 48, Folder 393)
    Peabody, Margaret The Peabody Museum Pearce, Claude Pearl, Marilyn Pearson, Mrs. James A. Pearson, James E. Pease, Richard M. Peavy, Paulina Pecquet Pederson, Emma A. Pederson, Mrs. Henry H. Peer, Lee Pei, I.M. Pekins, Frank W. Pembroke College Club Penaflor, Aurelio L. Jr. Pengley, Tao Penn State University Art Museum William Penn Memorial Museum
  - Peper - Peskin (Box 48, Folder 394)
    Peper, Niel Pepper, Beverly Pepsico Perez-Vega, Edmee Performing Arts Council Music Center, Los Angeles County Peridot Gallery (Joan Washburn) Perkins, Constance M. Perkins, Della Perkins, Granville Perls, Frank Perna, Gertrude Perret, Monique Perret-Gentil, Daisy Personetto, Joan Peskin, Roger M.
  - Peter - Pfuhl (Box 48, Folder 395)
    Peter, Joseph F. Peterman, E.C. Sr. Peters, Diane Peters, Howard J. Peters, Tassia Petersen, Roland Petersen, Mrs. S.K. Peterson, James K. Peterson, Marilyn Ives Petralia, G. Pettit, Ethel V. Petty Cash Petty, Opal Moore Pevsner Pflaum, Peter E. Pfuhl, Agnes Coggins
  - Phang - Pike (Box 48, Folder 396)
    Phang, Christine H. Pharr, Walter Nelson Philadelphia Museum of Art Philadelphia, PA Phil Bro Philbrook Art Center Phillips Collection Phillips, Jennie M. Phillips, Lawrence R. Phillips, Stephen Phoenix Gallery Piccone, Jorge A. Pierce, Patricia Pierce, Henry A. Pierelli, Attilio Pierpont, Agnes Harwood Pierpont Morgan Library Pierre, Jean Pietkiewicz, Andrew Pifer, Harry V. Jr Pike, Mildred Rhoda
  - Pirovano - Plymouth State College (Box 48, Folder 397)
    Pirovano, Ignacio Pitruzzella, Salvatore Pitt, Mrs. Hewitt Pittsfield Public Schools Plancher, Arnold Plantation Museum Plate, Walter SUNY Plattsburgh Playhouse Galleries Plaza Galleries Plexiglass, UV Filtering Plowden, Anna Plowers, Betty Plymouth State College
  - Poirrier - Portnow (Box 48, Folder 398)
    Poirrier, Regina L. Polasek, Joseph Polite, Janice M. Pollack, Barbara Pollack, Mrs. C. Martinez Pollitzer, Eric A.M. Polo Polomar Pomeroy, William A. Pool, Beekman H. Pooley, Derek Poor, Alfred Easton Pope, Kerig Porke, Bernard Poppe, Y. Porcelains Porteous, David Porter, David Porter, Eddie Porter, Victor W. Portinari Portland Museum Portland Art Museum Portman, Raymond H. Portnow, Julius and Marjorie
  - Portraits - Postman (Box 48, Folder 399)
    Portraits Poscher, Frank A. Posner, Dorothy Possollo, Guilherme Postman, Mrs. A.L.
  - Potter - Powers (Box 48, Folder 400)
    Potter, Norman S. Powe, Harold Powell, C.R. Powell, John R. Powell, Leslie Powers, Mrs. Edwin R., Sr. Powers, Ronald C.
  - Practicing Law Institute - Providencial Development Corporation (Box 49, Folder 401)
    Practicing Law Institute Prairie Company Prat, Jean-Louise Prati, Marcel Pratt Graphics Center Pratt Precedent Films Prescott, Kenneth W. Prescott, Linzee Previtali, James M. Pribyl, Carol Price, Mrs. George H. Price, Madeline F. Price, Irene Priest, Alan Princess Farid-es-Sultaneh Princeton University, The Art Museum Pringle, Roy Prins, Kimberly Jr. Private Collection Catalogue Probst, Joachim Proenza, Jose Prohaska, Ray Prokopoff, Stephen S. Propp, Mrs. Mortimer Protean Century Protetch, Max "Proud Possessors" - TV Program The Providencial Development Corporation
  - Practicing Law Institute - Providencial Development Corporation (Box 49, Folder 0401A)
  - Public Education Association - Pyrite (Box 49, Folder 402)
    Public Education Association Publicity Puccio, Mrs. Gaspare Pucker, Mr. and Mrs. B.H. Puerto Rico, Institute of Puerto Rican Culture Puffert, Christa Puglisi, Josephine Pulido, Mrs. Antonio Purcell, Robert W. Purdy, Clifford K. Puzinas, Mrs. Austra Pyle, Bobby Pyrite
  - Painting Conservation/Restoration, 1952-1976 (Box 49, Folder 403)
    Correspondence and memoranda re conservation work done on NAR paintings and credentials of conservation experts.
  - Paper Conservation/Restoration, 1950-1982 (Box 49, Folder 404)
    Correspondence and memoranda re conservation work done on NAR prints and credentials of conservation experts.
  - Parke-Bernet - Appraisals, 1970-1971 (Box 49, Folder 405)
    Correspondence and memoranda re appraisal of NAR art. Bill for appraisal.
  - Parke-Bernet - Receipts for Works Received by Parke-Bernet, 1971 (Box 49, Folder 406)
    Lists and receipts of items sent to Parke-Bernet for consignment.
  - Parke-Bernet - Sales, May 1973 (Box 49, Folder 407)
    Catalogs, lists of sold items, notification of sales and copies of checks sent to NAR in payment for sold artworks.
  - Parke-Bernet - Sales, June-August 1972 (Box 49, Folder 408)
  - Parke-Bernet - Sales, May 1972 (Box 49, Folder 409)
  - Parke-Bernet - Sales, March-May 1972 (Box 49, Folder 410)
  - Parke-Bernet - Sales, March 1972 (Box 49, Folder 411)
  - Parke-Bernet - Sales, March 1972 (Box 50, Folder 412)
  - Parke-Bernet - Sales, February 1972 (Box 50, Folder 413)
  - Parke-Bernet - Sales, January 1972 (Box 50, Folder 414)
  - Parke-Bernet - Sales, December 1971 (Box 50, Folder 415)
  - Parke-Bernet - Sales, November 1971 (Box 50, Folder 416)
  - Parke-Bernet - Sales, November 1971 (Box 50, Folder 417)
  - Parke-Bernet - Signed Contracts, 1971 (Box 50, Folder 418)
    Unsigned and signed contracts for NAR's consignment of art with Parke-Bernet.
  - Parke-Bernet - Signed Contracts, 1971 (Box 50, Folder 419)
  - Parvin, Robert, 1971-1976 (Box 51, Folder 420)
    Correspondence, memoranda and receipts for restoration work done on NAR Japanese screens.
  - Perls Galleries, 1953-1957, 1969-1971, 1976-1977 (Box 51, Folder 421)
    Correspondence, memoranda and lists of artworks sent to Perls for sale.
  - Personnel, 1966-1977 (Box 51, Folder 422)
    Correspondence, memoranda, resumes, schedules and salaries of individuals working with the art collection.
  - Photography, 1951-1977 (Box 51, Folder 423)
    Memoranda re orders for negatives or reprints. Lists of negative numbers.
  - Photography, 1951-1977 (Box 51, Folder 424)
  - Photography, 1951-1977 (Box 51, Folder 425)
  - Picasso, Pablo, 1950-1974 (Box 51, Folder 426)
    Memoranda and correspondence re purchases and loans of NAR Picasso pieces. News clippings re NAR Picasso pieces.
  - Picasso, Pablo (includes tapestries), 1950-1974 (Box 51, Folder 427)
  - Plastic Conservation/Restoration, 1973-1976 (Box 51, Folder 428)
    Memoranda and background material re plexiglass cases.
  - Pocker (frames), 1961-1977 (Box 51, Folder 429)
    Memoranda, correspondence and receipts for items delivered to Pocker for framing.
  - Pocker (frames), 1961-1977 (Box 51, Folder 430)
  - Pocker (frames), 1961-1977 (Box 51, Folder 431)
  - Press, 1974-1975 (Box 52, Folder 432)
    Correspondence re press coverage of NAR Collection. "Newsday" article, "Los Angeles Times."
  - Purcell, Robert, 1973 (Box 52, Folder 433)
    Memorandum and advertisements for the sale of Purcell's paintings.
  - Quadrani - Quix (Box 52, Folder 434)
    Quandrani, Odyssia S. (Galleria Odyssia) Quandt, Silvia Queen Elizabeth II Querido, Zita Query, Mrs. Aldrich Quigley, Goldie Quitzau, Gisela Quix, George
  - Rabin - Raymond (Box 52, Folder 435)
    Rabin, Bernard Rachna Radovanovitch, George Ragan, Phillip Ragheb, Mohamed Manget-Rai, Mary Rainone, Mrs. C.F. Rains, Baxter Ramans, Modris Rambusch, Viggo Bech Ramon, Alfredo Ranasinghe, Alex Rancourt, Mrs. Robert J. Rand, Harry Randall, Doanda Rankin, J.T. Rapp, F.W. Rash, Judy L. Rashap, Arthur W. Rathbone, Perry Rathbun, William Rauch, Charles E. Ravenal, Richard Ravenel, Gaillard F. Ray, Rudolph Raymond & Raymond Raymond, Susan F. Raymond, Mrs. Wayte
  - Reading - Remmel (Box 52, Folder 436)
    Reading, John T. Reams, Ron Rebours, Pierre Reder, Bernard Reed, Mrs. George R. Reed, Mrs. J.H. Reese of Brewer-Cantelmo Co. Reese, Lucile Reese, SW & Co. Reid, Ruth P. Reiff, Hal Frank Reilly's School of Art (Frank Reilly Heritage Foundation) Reindel, Edna Reis, Bernard Reiss-Cohen Reiss, Wallace Relis, Rochelle Re-Matting Rembrandt Remick, Joan Remington Art Museum Remmel, Robert
  - Renaud - Rhode Island School of Design (Box 52, Folder 437)
    Renaud, Roger Rendon, Harvey Rennolds, Edna R. Renoir, Washer Woman Renucci, Jacqueline Renwick Gallery Renzoni, Lorenzo Repkay, C. Republican Government Conference Requa, Leonard F. Jr. Reuther Reynolds Gay Reynolds, Joshua Rheinhardt, Ad Rhoda Sande Gallery Rhode Island School of Design
  - Rice - Richards, Ann (Box 52, Folder 438)
    Rice, Edward Richards, Ann (Ann Richards Gallery)
  - Richards, John - Riley (Box 52, Folder 439)
    Richards, John Richardson, James Richardson, John Richardson Reflector Company Richenburg, Mrs. Robert Richenburg, Robert Richey, Mrs. Clyde W. Richmond, Oliffe Rickey, George W. Riesco, Elvira de Undurraga Rieser, Jacques K. Rights and Reproductions Rigling, Ernest Rickey, Mrs. George Riland, W. Kenneth Riley, Mrs. Beech Riley, Dotti (Gallery III) Riley, James J.
  - Rina Gallery - Rivers (Box 52, Folder 440)
    Rina Gallery Ringling (John and Mable Ringling Museum of Art) Rings Rickberg, Ellen Ringwald, Ringwood Manor House Rio Grande Graphics Ripley, Dillon Ripon Society Ritchie, Andrew C. Rivas, Dagobert Rivers, Reva
  - Roads Galleries - Roberts (Box 53, Folder 441)
    Roads Galleries Robbin, Rand Robbins, Gordon Robbins, Guy F. Robbins, Terrence Robedee, Carl L. Roberson, Mrs. Albert Roberson Center for Arts and Sciences Roberts, Betty Roberts, Charles A. Roberts, David Roberts, Mrs. Erling Roberts, Iva Lee Roberts, Neva E. Roberts, Vivian Roberts, William K.
  - Robertson - Robert Taylor Martin (Mrs.) (Box 53, Folder 442)
    Robertson, Bryan Robertson, Mrs. T.J.
  - Robertson - Robert Taylor Martin (Mrs.) (Box 53, Folder 0442A)
    Restrcted material
  - Robins - Rochester Memorial Art Gallery (Box 53, Folder 443)
    Robins, Mrs. Eli Robinson, Mrs. A.O. Robinson, Dorothy Robinson, Gladys Lloyd Robinson, Steven Robinson, Theodore Robles, Felix G. Robles, Luis Gonzalez Rochambeau Chateau Rochepierre Rochelle Thomas, A.P. Rochester, Channel 21 Rochester Memorial Art Gallery
  - Rockefeller Center - Roosa (Box 53, Folder 444)
    Rockefeller Center, Inc. Rockefeller University Rodgers, Mrs. Churchill Rodgers, W. John Rodin, Auguste Rodriguez, Georges Roethel, Hans Rogers, Millard F. Rogers, William D. Rogo, Else Rohlfing, Christian Roman Bronz Works Romanelli, Carl Rombauer, Mrs. Rome & Haas, Philadelphia Ronan, W. Roosa, Carol
  - Rosa - Rosenquist (Box 53, Folder 445)
    Rosa, Frank Rosalsky, Sara A. Rose, Arthur Rose, D.G. Rose, Mary L. Rose, Mrs. Maurice W. Peter Rose Gallery Rose, William Paul Rosenburg & Co. Rosenfeld, Joshua Rosenfield, Robert Rosengart, Siegfried Rosenquist, Jan
  - Rosa - Rosenquist (Box 53, Folder 0445A)
  - Rosenthal - Rote (Box 53, Folder 446)
    Rosenthal, Abraham Rosenthal, Joseph Stanley Rosenthal, Seymour Rosenzweig, Harry Rosenzweig, Kenneth Rosner, Diane Ross, Gloria Rosson, Gertrude McMahon Rostand, Michael Rostow, W.W. Rote, John
  - Rosenthal - Rote (Box 53, Folder 0446A)
  - Roth - Rottschaefer (Box 53, Folder 447)
    Roth, Allen Roth, David Roth, Frank Roth, George Roth, Jerry Roth, Nathan I. Roth, Richard Roth, Mr. and Mrs. Richard Rothmans of Pallmall, Canada, LTD Rothschild, Carolyn Rothschild, Sigmund Rottschaefer, Mrs. B.W.
  - Roth - Rottschaefer (Box 53, Folder 0447A)
    Rothenberg Obder Tauber
  - Rouault - Rozan-Barker (Box 53, Folder 448)
    Rouault, Georges Rounak, Mrs. A.W. Round, T.E. Rowan, Robert A. Rowe, Robert Roy, Marc Royal Marcks Gallery Rozan-Barker, Gertrude
  - Rubinstein - Ryback (Box 53, Folder 449)
    Rubinstein, Marion Rubinstein, Erica Beckh Rubin, Harold Rubin, William Rubner, Maurice Rucker, P. Ruebhausen, Oscar M. Ruggles, John Rugs, Oriental Ruin, Taya Louise Rukawina, Emma Rummell, Mrs. Robert W. Sr. Rumsey, Claire Runyon-Winchell Gallery Russell, Carolyn Russell, Ms. David E. Russell, Jack L. Russomanno, Mrs. M.C. Ru-Tao-Kyi Ruwe, Mrs. E.M. Ruzicka, Wilhelm Ryback, Joseph
  - Rubinstein - Ryback (Box 53, Folder 0449A)
  - Rockefeller, Abby Aldrich, Oriental Art (Box 54, Folder 451)
    Binder of lists, descriptions and some pictures of pieces in the Abby Aldrich Rockefeller Oriental Art collection.
  - Rockefeller, Barbara O., 1971-1974 (Box 54, Folder 452)
    Correspondence re Cultural Society of America American Works Project. Proposal for said program.
  - Rockefeller, Blanchette H., 1950, 1955, 1970 (Box 54, Folder 453)
    Letter from NAR re participation in Special Art Fund.
  - Rockefeller, Laurance, 1965-1982 (Box 54, Folder 455)
    Memoranda and correspondence re identification and purchases of artworks.
  - Rockefeller, Laurance, 1965-1982 (Box 54, Folder 0455A)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance, 1965-1982 (Box 54, Folder 456)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance, 1965-1982 (Box 54, Folder 457)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance, 1965-1982 (Box 54, Folder 0457A)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance, 1965-1982 (Box 54, Folder 458)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance, 1965-1982 (Box 54, Folder 0458A)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance, 1965-1982 (Box 54, Folder 459)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance, 1965-1982 (Box 54, Folder 460)
  - Rockefeller, Martha Baird, 1971 (Box 55, Folder 462)
    List of artworks and their values. These pieces were obtained by NAR at the time of Martha Baird Rockefeller's death.
  - Rockefeller, Mary Clark, 1962 (Box 55, Folder 463)
    List of items given to Mary Clark Rockefeller in the separation agreement. List of items returned to NAR.
  - Rockefeller, Mary Clark, 1962 (Box 55, Folder 0463A)
  - Rockefeller, Rodman, 1971-1974 (Box 55, Folder 465)
    Memoranda re gifts from NAR and possible purchases.
  - Rockefeller, Sydney Roberts, 1975 (Box 55, Folder 467)
    Letter to NAR re exhibit of contemporary Chinese Art.
  - Rockefeller, Winthrop, 1971-1975 (Box 55, Folder 468)
    Memoranda re "Virgin and Child" sculpture.
  - Saarinen - Saeki (Box 55, Folder 469)
    Saarinen, Aline Sabado, Gil V. Sacchi, Guiseppe Sachs, A.M. Sachs, Mrs. Alexander Sachs, Robert Sadagopan, Barbara Sadowska, Mrs. Sadowsky, Harriet Saeki
  - Saginaw Valley College - Samuels (Box 55, Folder 470)
    Saginaw Valley College Saidenberg, Eleanor Saidenberg Gallery Saidenberg, Daniel St. Gil, Dianne St. Louis, City Art Museum of St. Mary's College Sakowitz, Robert T. Sales Salinas, Baruj Salles, George Salmony, Alfred Salpeter, Harry Samoiloff, Carlene
  - Saginaw Valley College - Samuels (Box 55, Folder 0470A)
  - San Antonio Art League - Sayles (Box 55, Folder 471)
    San Antonio Art League San Antonio Museum Association Sanchez, Reverand Carlos Sanchez-Bustamente, Luz Sanders Sandler, Alvin Sandoval, Corliss Sandoval, Judith Hancock de Sandt, Walter San Francisco Museum of Art Santilli, John Santini Bros., Inc. Saperstein, Sol M. Saphire, Larry Saracco, Sebastian Saratoga Racing Centennial (Saratoga Spa) Saratoga Springs, Chamber of Commerce Sasko, Rita Saturday Review Saulpaugh, Ivane Sava, Maximilian Savage, Philip Savarkar, Ruth Savelle, Isabelle Sawyer, Hugh E. Sawyer, Stan Sayles, Eva Sayles, L.
  - Scafette - Scherer (Box 55, Folder 472)
    Scarfetta, Stefano Scagano, Jerry Scally, Neil Scarsdale Woman's Club, Inc. Schab, William H. Schaefer, Bertha Schayes, Naomi Schector, Sylvia Schein, Donald Schell, Sherril V. Schellam, Mrs. Fred Schempp, Theodore Schenectady Auction Schenectady Museum Schepis, Angelo Scherer, Franz
  - Schiavone - Schnittman (Box 55, Folder 473)
    Schiavone Schickler, Jerome Schillinger, Mrs. Joseph Schindle, Mollie Schlichter, Florence Schlifstein, Sylvia Schmeckebier, Laurence Schmidbaur, Benno Schmidt, Bette Jean Schmidt, L.B. Schnaer, Sol Schnare, Marbeth Schnaufer, Irma Schnebelen, Pierre Schneider, Geraldine Scheider, Mrs. Glen Schneider, Irma Schneier, Donna F.
  - Schiavone - Schnittman (Box 55, Folder 0473A)
    Schleyen, Mrs. G. Schlothauer, Mrs. Gary Schnittman, F.K.A.
  - Schoellkopf - Schuyler (Box 55, Folder 474)
    School of Chinese Brushwork, Inc. Schoonmaker, Mrs. Earl Schottlander, Bernard Schram, James S. Schriever, George Schroter, Louise Schuller, Grete Schuller, Mr. and Mrs. Joachim Schulman, Max Schulte-Ladbeck, Bernd Schultz, Mrs. Joseph Schulz, John Schuman, Jacquelyne Schumm Traffic Agency Inc. Schummelfeder, Ms. S. Schuyler, Cortlandt
  - Schoellkopf - Schuyler (Box 55, Folder 0474A)
    Schoellkopf, George (Schoellkopf Gallery)
  - Schwartz - Sculpture (Box 56, Folder 475)
    Schwartz, Aubrey Schwartz, Leonard Schwarz, Manfred Schwoebel, Lyle W. Scliar, Carlos Scoffins, Robert Christopher Scopinich, Robert Scott, Mrs. David B. Scotton, Frank Scribner, R. Glyde Scroll Box Scudder Gallery Sculptors Guild, Inc. Sculpture Bases Sculpture Conservation/Restoration Sculpture NOW, Inc.
  - Searles - Seiferle (Box 56, Folder 476)
    Searles, Mrs. Quentin Seattle Art Museum Seckler, Mrs. Ned S. Security Storage Company Seese, Laura M. Sefsik, Mrs. Stephen Segal, SHOWER CURTAIN, base Segal, George Segal, Michael M. Segy Gallery Sehring, George Seibold, C.E. Seidman, I.S. Seiferle, Mrs. A. Mase
  - Searles - Seiferle (Box 56, Folder 0476A)
    Segnini, Ildegar Perez
  - Seley - Seymour (Box 56, Folder 477)
    Seley, Jason Selig, Minna Jacques Seligmann & Co., Inc. Selkowitz, Judith Selz, Peter Senate Sendlinger, Annie D. Serger, Helen Serpan Serru, Arnold Seton Hall University Setterberg, Ruth Sevitin, Joseph Sevits, Hyman W. Sexton, Lloyd Seybolt, George C. Seymour, Mrs. George D.
  - Shaffer - Sherwood (Box 56, Folder 478)
    Shaffer, Muriel Shahn, Ben Shakerley, Geoffrey Shannon, Carol Sharrett, Simone Sharkey, Edward Sharkey, Margaret Sharpe, Mrs. A. Shaw, Ernie Sheers, Harriet Sherekjian, Haig Shepherd Gallery Shepherd, Mrs. Lloyd Shepard, Lynn Shepherd, Sheldon Sherlock, Jerry Sherman, Jerry Liza Sherman Corporate Art Sherwood, Grace M.
  - Shiflet - Shrubsole (Box 56, Folder 479)
    Shiflet, Charles, E. Shimabukuro, Isami Shirae, Shiro Z. Shlau, David Shore Galleries Shore, Lily Shorewood Reporductions Shorewood Publishers, Inc. Shorter, Mrs. N.M. Shrubsole, S.J.
  - Shiflet - Shrubsole (Box 56, Folder 0479A)
    Shipway, Margery Shrady, Frederick
  - Shulman - Shuster Gallery (Box 56, Folder 480)
    Shulman, Arline Shuman, Lucy Marie Shumylowych, Taras Shurkin, Mrs. Walter Shuster Gallery
  - Shulman - Shuster Gallery (Box 56, Folder 0480A)
    Shure, Edward G.
  - Sibyl - Simms (Box 56, Folder 481)
    Sibyl, Sidney Janis Gallery Siegal, Raphael Siegal, Walter Siegesmund, Carl E. Silberman Galleries Silicone Silver, Cathy Silverman, Arthur Silverman, Dorothea Silverton, Mike Silvester, David Simmons, Louis A. Simms, Virginia F.
  - Sibyl - Simms (Box 56, Folder 0481A)
    Silverman, Jacob
  - Simon - Sirugo (Box 56, Folder 482)
    Simon, Ellen Simone, John Simons, Nancy Simonson, Clifford Simpson, Randolph L. Singer, Harry Singh Sinsabaugh, Mrs. Charles F. (re Cope Gallery) Sipos, Walter Sirena Sittig, Frederick V. Sirovich Senior Center Sirugo, Sal
  - Simon - Sirugo (Box 56, Folder 0482A)
    Simpson, William Kelly
  - Sisenweins - Skyllas (Box 56, Folder 483)
    Sisenweins, Mrs. Sidney Sister Bianca Sisti, Tony Sivers, Kent Skaalegaard, Mrs. M.D. Skerritt, Elizabeth Skidmore College Sklavos, N. Skowhegan School Skyllas, Drosso P.
  - Slade - Smith, Cecil (Box 56, Folder 484)
    Slade, Roy Slatkin, Charles E. Sleepy Hollow Restorations Sloane, Eric Sloan-Kettering Memorial Hospital Slocum, Mrs. L.E. Slotnick, Mortimer H. Small, Virginia Smallman, Margorie Smeal, Mrs. Eugene A. Smidt, Donna C. Smith, C. Smith, Carleton Smith, Mrs. Cecil Jr.
  - Smith, Charles - Smith, Peter (Box 57, Folder 485)
    Smith, Charles Augustus Smith, Charles R. Smith, Clare Smith, Clyde Smith, Dorothy Swale Smith, David (his daughters Candida and Rebecca) Smith, David Smith, H. Kerner Smith, Harold W. Smith, Harold V. Smith, Jack Smith, James Walton Smith, Lois Stewart Smith, Mark L. Smith, Marshall Smith, Norman C. Smith, Peter
  - Smith, Ralph - Smyth (Box 57, Folder 486)